<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Baguio City</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="category_image">Image</string>
    <string name="place_image">place image</string>

    <!-- Cafe -->
    <string name="cafe_a">Beyond Baguio Cafe and Restaurant</string>
    <string name="cafe_b">Stella Cafe</string>
    <string name="cafe_c">Choco-late de Batirol</string>
    <string name="cafe_d">Arcas Yard</string>
    <string name="cafe_e">Ginto Cafe</string>

    <string name="cafe_details_a">Beyond Baguio Cafe offers a modern yet Cordilleran interior design and a wide al fresco dining space, providing an astonishing atmosphere for a peaceful and quiet dining experience. The food, including rice meals and pasta, is tasty but may not always be served hot. The cafes delicious coffee and blueberry cheesecake are highly recommended for satisfying cravings.</string>
    <string name="cafe_details_b">Stella Cafe and Bar at The Cullinan Hotel offers a delightful al fresco dining experience with a relaxed ambiance. Drawing inspiration from Paris, this charming establishment is located on the ground floor of the Southern Sun Cullinan Hotel. Guests can savor South Africas finest wines while being guided by their resident sommelier in an intimate wine room. To further enhance the experience, visitors can enjoy refreshing afternoon drinks by the stunning pool terrace and indulge in delectable dishes from the seasonal menu.</string>
    <string name="cafe_details_c">Feeling cold from the breeze? Head over to this Baguio cafe in Camp John Hay for a warm hug in a mug! This charming place features traditional Filipino hot chocolate, made with the good stuff - local cacao beans! But wait, theres more! They also have fantastic coffee and yummy local treats like bibingka and suman to complete your Filipino merienda experience.</string>
    <string name="cafe_details_d">Arcas Yard, more than just a cafe, is a peaceful haven where you can get away from the rush of the city. Its tucked away amid the greenery on the edges of Baguio. It also offers a special concept, combining a cafe, library, and museum in one place. This hidden gem, surrounded by stunning views of the mountains, has a tranquil ambiance thats ideal for relaxing with a cup of freshly prepared coffee or herbal tea.</string>
    <string name="cafe_details_e">Mix coffee and comedy at this Baguio cafe! Not your average joe (pun intended), its a creative space where folks can sip on local specialty coffee and tea, exchange ideas, and maybe even crack a few jokes. Plus, theyve got a whole menu of breakfast treats, pastas, and sandwiches to make your tummy happy. Its the perfect spot to unleash your inner comedian (or just appreciate some good stand-up) with a cup of brew in hand!</string>

    <!-- Churches -->
    <string name="church_a">Baguio Cathedral of Our Lady of the Atonement</string>
    <string name="church_b">St. Joseph the Worker Parish Church</string>
    <string name="church_c">St. Vincent Ferrer Church</string>
    <string name="church_d">Holy Family Parish Church - Bakakeng North, Baguio City, Benguet (Diocese of Baguio)</string>
    <string name="church_e">St. John Don Bosco Parish Church - Trancoville, Baguio City, Benguet</string>

    <string name="church_details_a">The Catholic cathedral in Baguio City, Philippines is a stunning building with a distinctive pink façade and rose window. It is popular for its beauty and is one of the top tourist destinations in Baguio City.</string>
    <string name="church_details_b">St. Joseph the Worker Parish Church is situated in the Pacdal Circle area, making it a convenient stop for families visiting nearby attractions such as Botanical Garden, Wright Park, the Mansion, and Mines View Park. It is well-organized with ample parking space and has undergone renovations including a designated cry room for families with young children. The churchs spacious interior and adjacent prayer rooms provide a serene environment for visitors to engage in quiet reflection or candle lighting.</string>
    <string name="church_details_c">St. Vincent Ferrer Church, the earliest religious establishment in Baguio, predates the well-known Baguio Cathedral. This sacred place served as a mission station for Catholic missionaries before the Cathedrals construction. Located outside the city center, it offers a tranquil environment for devout individuals to engage in prayer and worship. Notably, this church also houses a columbarium where loved ones can find eternal rest.</string>
    <string name="church_details_d">Holy Family Parish Church in Bakakeng North, Baguio City, Benguet is a spacious and beautifully designed Catholic church with a huge altar and high ceilings. It is located in a serene area within the community, offering a peaceful environment for prayer and reflection. The church is known for its active engagement with youth members and hosts various activities. Despite its remote location, it is easily accessible by jeepney from Baguio Plaza.</string>
    <string name="church_details_e">St. John Don Bosco Parish Church in Trancoville, Baguio City is a serene and peaceful place to visit, especially during weekdays to avoid the crowds. If you attend Sunday mass, be sure to arrive early for a good seat. On Sundays and holidays, the church is surrounded by vendors selling religious items and souvenirs. The church offers a tranquil environment with ample parking space and is well-maintained despite needing some wall painting.</string>

    <!-- Bars -->
    <string name="bars_a">The Ampersand</string>
    <string name="bars_b">Basmnt</string>
    <string name="bars_c">Spade Superclub</string>
    <string name="bars_d">Albertos Bar</string>
    <string name="bars_e">Vesper Sports Bar</string>

    <string name="bars_details_a">The Ampersand is a popular nightclub located in the heart of Baguio City, within The Camp, which is known as the city\'s nightlife hub. It attracts a young crowd, mainly college-age young adults and young professionals. The club features vibrant dance tunes played by energetic DJs, making it an ideal spot for those looking to dance the night away. On weekends, the venue tends to get crowded, so timing your visit is crucial..</string>
    <string name="bars_details_b">Basmnt is a pub located inside Ritz Legarda hotel in Baguio City. It offers great views of the city from its basement and is perfect for relaxing after a day of sightseeing or excitement. The pub has an extensive menu with plenty of options for food and drink, as well as some hearty meals if youre looking to refuel.</string>
    <string name="bars_details_c">If you\'re in the mood to party, then Spade Superclub is the place for you! They usually have guest DJs and performers who will keep patrons entertained all night long. As for food and drinks, youre going to have a great time eating and drinking!</string>
    <string name="bars_details_d">Albertos Bar is a popular spot among locals in Baguio, offering a vibrant atmosphere and live music that ranges from beloved American country tunes to traditional Cordilleran melodies. The bar exudes a fantastic vibe, with talented performers and a wide selection of drinks and food. While the music can be quite loud, creating an energetic ambiance where dancing is encouraged, it may not be the best choice for those seeking a more relaxed setting for conversation.</string>
    <string name="bars_details_e">Vesper Sports Bar is a popular spot for sports and socializing. It has a wide selection of beers and cocktails, as well as TVs for watching the game. The atmosphere is relaxed and friendly, and theres usually plenty of seating available.</string>

    <!-- Parks -->
    <string name="parks_a">Burnham Park</string>
    <string name="parks_b">Mines View Park</string>
    <string name="parks_c">Mirador Heritage And Eco Park</string>
    <string name="parks_d">Baguio Botanical Garden</string>
    <string name="parks_e">Mt. Pulag National Park</string>

    <string name="parks_details_a">The mother of all parks in Baguio city, the summer capital of the Philippines, is a 32.84-hectare park designed by, and named after, American architect and urban planner Daniel Hudson Burnham, who also designed the original plan for Baguio City as well as Dewey Boulevard (now Roxas Boulevard) in Manila. The park has 12 main areas, the most popular of which are the Burnham Lagoon, a man-made lake with rowboats for hire; a childrens playground; a skating rink; the Rose Garden and the Picnic Grove.</string>
    <string name="parks_details_b">Mines View Park is one of the famous tourist spots across Baguio, packed with shops selling snacks, trinkets, botanical items, and others. Picture-taking services with traditional Igorot clothes, horses, dogs, and more are also available in the lower half of the park. The park also overlooks nearby mountains, forests, and Itogons abandoned mines.</string>
    <string name="parks_details_c">Mirador Heritage and Eco-Park is one of the newest destinations in Baguio City. It is located where the famed Lourdes Grotto stands. The park is huge, covering the top of Mirador Hill. Some parts of the park are based on known tourist destinations in Kyoto, Japan, including the Arashiyama Bamboo Grove and the Tori Gate at the Mirador Peace Memorial. Aside from those, the park houses the Jesuit Villa and Retreat House and Cafe Inigo by Ebai.</string>
    <string name="parks_details_d">Baguio Botanical Garden is a picturesque park located in Baguio City, Philippines. It offers visitors a peaceful escape with its lush greenery, colorful flowers, and scenic landscapes. The garden features a variety of plants, both native and ornamental, as well as quaint pathways, bridges, and native-style huts. Its also known for its cultural and artistic elements, including sculptures and traditional Igorot huts, providing a glimpse into the indigenous heritage of the region. Ideal for nature lovers and families, the garden is a serene space for leisurely walks, picnics, and photography.</string>
    <string name="parks_details_e">The Park has a large diversity of flora and fauna, many of which are endemic to the mountain. Its wildlife includes threatened mammals such as the Philippine Brown Deer, Northern Luzon Giant Cloud Rat and the Luzon Pygmy Fruit Bat.  One can also find several orchid species some of which are possibly endemic to Mt. Pulag, and other rare flora such as the pitcher plant.</string>

    <!-- Museums -->
    <string name="museums_a">BenCab Museum</string>
    <string name="museums_b">Museo Kordilyera</string>
    <string name="museums_c">Baguio Museum</string>
    <string name="museums_d">Bell House Library Museum</string>
    <string name="museums_e">Tam-Awan Village</string>

    <string name="museums_details_a">A visit to Baguio would not be complete without a stop at the BenCab Museum located in Tuba, Benguet. It is owned and named after National Artist Benedicto Cabrera, whose mastery ranges from painting to printmaking and beyond.            Inside the museum, you can marvel at Cabrera’s works plus the masterpieces of other renowned Filipino artists. His collection of ethnic wood carvings from the Ifugao tribe are also on display. BenCab also has a refreshing garden and an in-house restaurant, Cafe Sabel, where guests can relax or enjoy a quick meal.</string>
    <string name="museums_details_b">For those who want to dive deeper into the history and culture of the Cordillera Region, add Museo Kordilyera to your Baguio museum-hopping list. The ethnographic museum features a range of artifacts that will give visitors a deeper understanding of the indigenous tribes who live in Northern Luzon. It includes items from the Kalingas, Bontocs, and Ifugaos, among others.
Museo Kordilyera is located inside the University of the Philippines Baguio, has three floors full of artwork and artifacts, as well as a cafe and a small souvenir shop open to all guests. </string>
    <string name="museums_details_c">Baguio Museum is another gallery dedicated to the preservation of the city’s cultural heritage. However, art buffs will still have a great time here. For starters, the museum’s architectural design is inspired by the traditional Ifugao homes, evident in the predominant use of wood and stone on the facade alone. Inside, you’ll find intricate dioramas, tribal artifacts, and other items showcasing the life of the various indigenous groups that call the Cordillera Region home.
Baguio Museum also hosts exhibitions and shows. Best to follow their social media page for any upcoming events.</string>
    <string name="museums_details_d">The Bell House Library Museum may not be your usual museum in Baguio, but it’s still worth checking out. The unique attraction inside Camp John Hay was designed by General J. Franklin Bell and was used as a rest house by the Commanding General of the Philippines. Art and architecture aficionados will be impressed by its American-style design and its cozy interiors.
Near the Bell House, you can also check out the Bell Amphitheater and the Cemetery of Negativity, both of which are part of Camp John Hay’s historical core.</string>
    <string name="museums_details_e">Tam-Awan Village is a one-of-a-kind creative community located in Pinsao Proper. It aims to promote the rich heritage of the Cordilleran people and, at the same time, showcase the works of local artists.         Some of Tam-Awans most noticeable features include its collection of Kalinga and Ifugao huts, endless display of Cordillera artistry, and the cozy Tam-Awan Village Cafe. They also have a new attraction in the works called the Igorot Stone Kingdom.</string>
</resources>
